// old
const nbaQuizQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history?",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which team won the most NBA championships in the 1990s?",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Chicago Bulls",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game?",
    options: [
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "David Thompson",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which NBA player is known as 'The Answer'?",
    options: ["Shaquille O'Neal", "Tim Duncan", "Allen Iverson", "Dwyane Wade"],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Who won the NBA Most Valuable Player (MVP) award for the 2020-2021 season?",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "LeBron James",
      "James Harden",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "N/A (Giannis Antetokounmpo)",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What team drafted Dirk Nowitzki before he was traded to the Dallas Mavericks in 1998?",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Which NBA team is known for their 'Showtime' era during the 1980s?",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Who is the tallest player in NBA history?",
    options: ["Shaquille O'Neal", "Yao Ming", "Manute Bol", "Gheorghe Mureșan"],
    correctAnswer: "Gheorghe Mureșan",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career points per game average in NBA history?",
    options: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "How many NBA championships did Michael Jordan win during his career?",
    options: ["3", "5", "6", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "6",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most triple-doubles in a single NBA season?",
    options: [
      "Magic Johnson",
      "LeBron James",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Larry Bird",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Kobe Bryant in the 1996 NBA Draft before trading him to the Lakers?",
    options: [
      "Charlotte Hornets",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Vancouver Grizzlies",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Charlotte Hornets",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Who is the only player in NBA history to record a quadruple-double in a game?",
    options: [
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "David Robinson",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Nate Thurmond",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Which NBA team is known for its 'Bad Boys' era during the late 1980s?",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Detroit Pistons",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who is the youngest player to score 70 or more points in a single NBA game?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Kobe Bryant", "Kevin Durant", "Devin Booker"],
    correctAnswer: "Devin Booker",
  },
];
export default nbaQuizQuestions;
// old

export const legendPlayers = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who is often referred to as 'The Black Mamba' in the NBA?",
    options: ["Michael Jordan", "Magic Johnson", "Kobe Bryant", "Larry Bird"],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which NBA legend is known for his famous 'Sky Hook' shot?",
    options: [
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Larry Bird",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who holds the record for the most assists in NBA history?",
    options: ["Magic Johnson", "John Stockton", "Steve Nash", "Chris Paul"],
    correctAnswer: "John Stockton",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which NBA legend was known for his 'Dream Shake' move?",
    options: [
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Tim Duncan",
      "David Robinson",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who is often called 'The Admiral' in the NBA?",
    options: ["Tim Duncan", "Karl Malone", "David Robinson", "Patrick Ewing"],
    correctAnswer: "David Robinson",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which NBA legend is known as 'His Airness'?",
    options: ["Larry Bird", "Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Michael Jordan"],
    correctAnswer: "Michael Jordan",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who won the NBA Most Valuable Player (MVP) award six times during the 1960s and 1970s?",
    options: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "Oscar Robertson",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which NBA legend is known for his famous 'Sky Hook' shot?",
    options: [
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Larry Bird",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game?",
    options: [
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Elgin Baylor",
      "David Thompson",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which NBA legend is known as 'The Answer'?",
    options: ["Shaquille O'Neal", "Tim Duncan", "Allen Iverson", "Dwyane Wade"],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Who won the NBA Most Valuable Player (MVP) award for the 2020-2021 season?",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "LeBron James",
      "James Harden",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "What team drafted Dirk Nowitzki before he was traded to the Dallas Mavericks in 1998?",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which NBA team is known for their 'Showtime' era during the 1980s?",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Who is the tallest player in NBA history?",
    options: ["Shaquille O'Neal", "Yao Ming", "Manute Bol", "Gheorghe Mureșan"],
    correctAnswer: "Gheorghe Mureșan",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Which player has the highest career points per game average in NBA history?",
    options: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
];

export const legendsTeams = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which team did Larry Bird spend his entire NBA career with?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "With which team did Shaquille O'Neal win three consecutive NBA championships from 2000 to 2002?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Orlando Magic",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Tim Duncan with the first overall pick in the 1997 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "San Antonio Spurs",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "For which team did Hakeem Olajuwon win two NBA championships in the 1990s?",
    options: [
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Phoenix Suns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Houston Rockets",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which team did Magic Johnson lead to five NBA championships during the 1980s?",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which team did Kareem Abdul-Jabbar play for before joining the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    options: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "With which team did Karl Malone spend the majority of his career before briefly joining the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Utah Jazz",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Phoenix Suns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Utah Jazz",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Allen Iverson as the first overall pick in the 1996 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Charlotte Hornets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Philadelphia 76ers",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "For which team did Bill Russell win 11 NBA championships during his career?",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "With which team did Oscar Robertson spend the majority of his career?",
    options: [
      "Cincinnati Royals",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cincinnati Royals",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Which team did Elgin Baylor play for throughout his entire NBA career?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Francisco Warriors",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "New York Knicks",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Minneapolis/Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "With which team did David Robinson spend his entire NBA career?",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Phoenix Suns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "San Antonio Spurs",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Scottie Pippen before he became a key player for the Chicago Bulls?",
    options: [
      "Seattle SuperSonics",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Seattle SuperSonics",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "For which team did Charles Barkley play for the majority of his career before joining the Houston Rockets?",
    options: [
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Philadelphia 76ers",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Which team did Clyde Drexler play for before he was traded to the Houston Rockets and won an NBA championship?",
    options: [
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Portland Trail Blazers",
  },
];

// 2000s
export const nba2000s1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which player won the NBA MVP award for the 2000-2001 season?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal", "Tim Duncan", "Allen Iverson"],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which team won three consecutive NBA championships from 2000 to 2002?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who was known as 'The Answer' during his career in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal", "Tim Duncan", "Allen Iverson"],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which player set a single-game scoring record with 81 points in 2006?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Dirk Nowitzki", "Tracy McGrady"],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Who was the coach of the San Antonio Spurs during their championship wins in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Phil Jackson", "Larry Brown", "Gregg Popovich", "Pat Riley"],
    correctAnswer: "Gregg Popovich",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Dirk Nowitzki before he was traded to the Dallas Mavericks in 1998?",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Who was known as 'Big Diesel' in the 2000s NBA?",
    options: ["Tim Duncan", "Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal", "Dirk Nowitzki"],
    correctAnswer: "Shaquille O'Neal",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which team won the NBA championship in the 2008 season led by the 'Big Three'?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Which player was known for his 'Eurostep' move during the 2000s?",
    options: ["Manu Ginóbili", "Steve Nash", "LeBron James", "Chris Paul"],
    correctAnswer: "Manu Ginóbili",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who was the first overall pick in the 2003 NBA Draft?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Carmelo Anthony", "Chris Bosh", "Dwyane Wade"],
    correctAnswer: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Which team won the NBA championship in 2004 despite having a low regular season win-loss record?",
    options: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Detroit Pistons",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Who was the head coach of the Los Angeles Lakers during their championship run in the early 2000s?",
    options: ["Phil Jackson", "Pat Riley", "Gregg Popovich", "Larry Brown"],
    correctAnswer: "Phil Jackson",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which player was known for his 'Seven Seconds or Less' style of play in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Chris Paul", "Steve Nash", "Jason Kidd", "Tony Parker"],
    correctAnswer: "Steve Nash",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which team drafted Carmelo Anthony in the 2003 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Denver Nuggets",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Denver Nuggets",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who was the 'Big Fundamental' and cornerstone of the San Antonio Spurs in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Tim Duncan", "Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal", "Dirk Nowitzki"],
    correctAnswer: "Tim Duncan",
  },
];

export const nba2000s2 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which player won the NBA MVP award for the 2005-2006 season?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal", "Tim Duncan", "LeBron James"],
    correctAnswer: "Steve Nash",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which team ended the Los Angeles Lakers' championship streak in the early 2000s?",
    options: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Detroit Pistons",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Who was the leading scorer for the Dallas Mavericks in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Dirk Nowitzki", "Steve Nash", "Michael Finley", "Jason Terry"],
    correctAnswer: "Dirk Nowitzki",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which player was known for his 'Big Shot Rob' reputation in clutch moments?",
    options: ["Tim Duncan", "Kobe Bryant", "Robert Horry", "Chauncey Billups"],
    correctAnswer: "Robert Horry",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Who won the NBA championship in 2008 with the Boston Celtics after joining forces with Kevin Garnett and Ray Allen?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Dwyane Wade", "Chris Bosh", "Paul Pierce"],
    correctAnswer: "Paul Pierce",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which team did Tracy McGrady play for before joining the Houston Rockets?",
    options: [
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Orlando Magic",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "Sacramento Kings",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Toronto Raptors",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who was the head coach of the Detroit Pistons during their championship win in 2004?",
    options: ["Phil Jackson", "Pat Riley", "Larry Brown", "Gregg Popovich"],
    correctAnswer: "Larry Brown",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which team drafted Amar'e Stoudemire in the 2002 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Phoenix Suns",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which player was known as 'Agent Zero' in the 2000s NBA?",
    options: ["Dwyane Wade", "Gilbert Arenas", "Steve Francis", "Baron Davis"],
    correctAnswer: "Gilbert Arenas",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Who was the defensive anchor for the San Antonio Spurs during their championship runs in the 2000s?",
    options: ["Tim Duncan", "Bruce Bowen", "Manu Ginóbili", "Tony Parker"],
    correctAnswer: "Bruce Bowen",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Which team did Kevin Garnett play for before being traded to the Boston Celtics in 2007?",
    options: [
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Minnesota Timberwolves",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Who was known for his 'Stepover' moment during the 2001 NBA Finals?",
    options: [
      "Allen Iverson",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Reggie Miller",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which team won the NBA championship in 2009 led by Kobe Bryant and Pau Gasol?",
    options: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Orlando Magic",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Who was the head coach of the Miami Heat when they won their first NBA championship in 2006?",
    options: ["Pat Riley", "Stan Van Gundy", "Erik Spoelstra", "Avery Johnson"],
    correctAnswer: "Pat Riley",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Which player was known for his dazzling crossovers and handles in the 2000s NBA?",
    options: ["Chris Paul", "Steve Nash", "Jason Kidd", "Allen Iverson"],
    correctAnswer: "Allen Iverson",
  },
];

// 2010s
export const nba2010s1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who won the NBA MVP award for the 2010-2011 season?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Derrick Rose", "Kevin Durant", "Stephen Curry"],
    correctAnswer: "Derrick Rose",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which team won an NBA-record 73 games in the 2015-2016 regular season?",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Who is the all-time leader in three-pointers made in NBA history as of 2021?",
    options: ["Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "Reggie Miller", "Klay Thompson"],
    correctAnswer: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which player scored 60 points in his final NBA game in 2016?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Dwyane Wade", "Kobe Bryant", "Dirk Nowitzki"],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Who was the coach of the Miami Heat during their 'Big Three' era with LeBron James, Dwyane Wade, and Chris Bosh?",
    options: ["Erik Spoelstra", "Pat Riley", "Stan Van Gundy", "Larry Brown"],
    correctAnswer: "Erik Spoelstra",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Kawhi Leonard in the 2011 NBA Draft before he was traded to the San Antonio Spurs?",
    options: [
      "Sacramento Kings",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Indiana Pacers",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Indiana Pacers",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Splash Brothers' partnership with Stephen Curry in the Golden State Warriors?",
    options: [
      "Klay Thompson",
      "Draymond Green",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "DeMarcus Cousins",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Klay Thompson",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Kyrie Irving with the first overall pick in the 2011 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
      "New Orleans Hornets",
      "Washington Wizards",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cleveland Cavaliers",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Who was the first overall pick in the 2012 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Kyrie Irving",
      "Andrew Wiggins",
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which team won the NBA championship in 2011 led by Dirk Nowitzki?",
    options: [
      "Miami Heat",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Dallas Mavericks",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Who won the NBA MVP award in back-to-back seasons in 2018 and 2019?",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Stephen Curry",
      "LeBron James",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Which team did Chris Paul play for before being traded to the Los Angeles Clippers in 2011?",
    options: [
      "New Orleans Hornets",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Phoenix Suns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "New Orleans Hornets",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Who was known as 'The Brow' during his time with the New Orleans Pelicans?",
    options: [
      "Kawhi Leonard",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which team drafted Damian Lillard in the 2012 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Charlotte Bobcats",
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Portland Trail Blazers",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who was known for his 'Lob City' era with the Los Angeles Clippers?",
    options: ["Kawhi Leonard", "Chris Paul", "Blake Griffin", "DeAndre Jordan"],
    correctAnswer: "Chris Paul",
  },
];
export const nba2010s2 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which player won the NBA MVP award for the 2016-2017 season?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Stephen Curry", "James Harden", "Kevin Durant"],
    correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which team made an unprecedented comeback from a 3-1 deficit to win the NBA Finals in 2016?",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cleveland Cavaliers",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who is the youngest player to score 60 points in an NBA game?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Devin Booker"],
    correctAnswer: "Devin Booker",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which player is known for his 'Greek Freak' nickname in the NBA?",
    options: [
      "Luka Dončić",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Kristaps Porziņģis",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which team drafted Karl-Anthony Towns with the first overall pick in the 2015 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
      "New York Knicks",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Minnesota Timberwolves",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Who was known as 'The Beard' during his time with the Houston Rockets?",
    options: [
      "James Harden",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Chris Paul",
      "Dwight Howard",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "James Harden",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Which team did Kevin Durant join in 2016, forming a 'super team' with Stephen Curry and Klay Thompson?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Who won the NBA MVP award for the 2019-2020 season?",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Which player was known for his 'Mr. Triple-Double' performances during the 2010s?",
    options: [
      "Chris Paul",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "LeBron James",
      "Russell Westbrook",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which team did Kawhi Leonard lead to an NBA championship in 2019?",
    options: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Toronto Raptors",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Who was known for his 'Unibrow' nickname in the NBA?",
    options: [
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Andre Drummond",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Which team drafted Damian Lillard in the 2012 NBA Draft?",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Charlotte Bobcats",
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Portland Trail Blazers",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Who won the NBA MVP award for the 2012-2013 season?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Stephen Curry", "Chris Paul"],
    correctAnswer: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Which team won the NBA championship in 2013 and 2014 led by LeBron James and Dwyane Wade?",
    options: [
      "San Antonio Spurs",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Miami Heat",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Linsanity' run with the New York Knicks in 2012?",
    options: ["Jeremy Lin", "Kyrie Irving", "John Wall", "Ricky Rubio"],
    correctAnswer: "Jeremy Lin",
  },
];

// allstar
export const nbaAllStar1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who holds the record for the most NBA All-Star Game MVP awards?",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which player scored 41 points in the 2006 NBA All-Star Game, setting a record for the most points in an All-Star Game?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Kobe Bryant", "Allen Iverson", "Kevin Durant"],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "How many All-Star Game appearances did Tim Duncan make during his career?",
    options: ["10", "12", "14", "15"],
    correctAnswer: "15",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which player is known for his 'Lob City' era with the Los Angeles Clippers in the All-Star Game?",
    options: [
      "Chris Paul",
      "Blake Griffin",
      "DeAndre Jordan",
      "Jamal Crawford",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Chris Paul",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who was the MVP of the 2003 NBA All-Star Game?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Kobe Bryant", "Michael Jordan", "Kevin Garnett"],
    correctAnswer: "Kevin Garnett",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which player from the Dallas Mavericks participated in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2000s and 2010s?",
    options: ["Dirk Nowitzki", "Steve Nash", "Jason Kidd", "Michael Finley"],
    correctAnswer: "Dirk Nowitzki",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Greek Freak' nickname and has been an NBA All-Star multiple times in the 2010s and 2020s?",
    options: [
      "Luka Dončić",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Kristaps Porziņģis",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which player was selected as an NBA All-Star the most times during the 2000s?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Tim Duncan", "Allen Iverson"],
    correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most consecutive NBA All-Star Game selections?",
    options: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Tim Duncan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which player represented the Toronto Raptors in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2010s and 2020s?",
    options: ["DeMar DeRozan", "Kyle Lowry", "Vince Carter", "Chris Bosh"],
    correctAnswer: "Kyle Lowry",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "How many NBA All-Star Game MVP awards did Shaquille O'Neal win in his career?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Which player from the Miami Heat represented the team in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2000s and 2010s?",
    options: ["Dwyane Wade", "LeBron James", "Chris Bosh", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
    correctAnswer: "Dwyane Wade",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Who was the first overall pick in the 2018 NBA Draft and became an NBA All-Star in his second season?",
    options: ["Luka Dončić", "Zion Williamson", "Deandre Ayton", "Trae Young"],
    correctAnswer: "Zion Williamson",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Which player from the Oklahoma City Thunder became an NBA All-Star in his second season and was known for his triple-doubles?",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "James Harden",
      "Serge Ibaka",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Big KAT' nickname and has represented the Minnesota Timberwolves in NBA All-Star Games?",
    options: [
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Andrew Wiggins",
      "Jimmy Butler",
      "Kevin Love",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Karl-Anthony Towns",
  },
];
export const nbaAllStar2 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Which player scored 52 points in the 2019 NBA All-Star Game, setting a record for the most points in a recent All-Star Game?",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Stephen Curry",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kevin Durant",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "How many All-Star Game appearances did Chris Paul make during his career?",
    options: ["7", "9", "11", "13"],
    correctAnswer: "11",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Splash Brothers' partnership with Klay Thompson in the NBA All-Star Game?",
    options: [
      "Stephen Curry",
      "Draymond Green",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "DeMarcus Cousins",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which player from the Portland Trail Blazers became an NBA All-Star and was known for his clutch shooting?",
    options: [
      "Damian Lillard",
      "C.J. McCollum",
      "LaMarcus Aldridge",
      "Brandon Roy",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Damian Lillard",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who was the MVP of the 2012 NBA All-Star Game?",
    options: ["LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Stephen Curry", "Dwight Howard"],
    correctAnswer: "Kevin Durant",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Which player represented the Memphis Grizzlies in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2010s?",
    options: ["Mike Conley", "Marc Gasol", "Zach Randolph", "Rudy Gay"],
    correctAnswer: "Marc Gasol",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Greek Freak' nickname and has been an NBA All-Star multiple times in the 2010s and 2020s?",
    options: [
      "Luka Dončić",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Kristaps Porziņģis",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which player was selected as an NBA All-Star the most times during the 2010s?",
    options: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Kevin Durant", "Chris Paul"],
    correctAnswer: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most consecutive NBA All-Star Game selections?",
    options: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Tim Duncan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which player represented the Toronto Raptors in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2010s and 2020s?",
    options: ["DeMar DeRozan", "Kyle Lowry", "Vince Carter", "Chris Bosh"],
    correctAnswer: "Kyle Lowry",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "How many NBA All-Star Game MVP awards did LeBron James win in his career?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correctAnswer: "3",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Which player from the Miami Heat represented the team in multiple NBA All-Star Games in the 2010s and 2020s?",
    options: ["Dwyane Wade", "LeBron James", "Chris Bosh", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
    correctAnswer: "Dwyane Wade",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Who was the first overall pick in the 2018 NBA Draft and became an NBA All-Star in his second season?",
    options: ["Luka Dončić", "Zion Williamson", "Deandre Ayton", "Trae Young"],
    correctAnswer: "Zion Williamson",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Which player from the Oklahoma City Thunder became an NBA All-Star in his second season and was known for his triple-doubles?",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "James Harden",
      "Serge Ibaka",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Who is known for his 'Big KAT' nickname and has represented the Minnesota Timberwolves in NBA All-Star Games?",
    options: [
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Andrew Wiggins",
      "Jimmy Butler",
      "Kevin Love",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Karl-Anthony Towns",
  },
];
